本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
嘿  大家  注意了  重大消息
Okay, everybody. Listen up. Big announcement.
我的产假结束了  必须要回医院干活了
Maternity leave is over and I'm headed back to work at the hospital.
你能把托比带走吗
Can you take Toby with you?
宝贝  我想咱们谈过这个话题
Honey, I think we've been over this.
这就表示同意呗
Is that a yes?
好了 你俩要周六要看好这俩小不点
All right, you two are gonna take care of the little ones on Saturday.
泰迪  你来看托比
Teddy, you get Toby.
啊  为啥我不能看托比
Aw, why can't I have Toby?
你记不记得上次叫你看管个婴儿发生了什么事
Remember what happened the last time I put you in charge of a baby?
老兄  要弄丢个宝宝  你这辈子就被记住了
Man, you lose one kid. You get labeled for life.
你和盖比能来照顾查莉
You and Gabe can take care of Charlie.
那老爸做什么
What about Dad?
还是说你信不过这又老又粗心的家伙
Or don't you trust old butterfingers?
伙计  你弄掉过两个宝宝
Man. You drop two babies...
我刚想起来这周六我得去中学生联合国大会
I just remembered I have the student UN on Saturday.
-那是在中午  -哦  那不成问题
- It's at noon.- Oh, that's not a problem.
我只工作半天
I only work half a day.
这样吧  我去学校找你
You know what? I'll meet you at the
我们来交接托比
high school, we'll do a Toby hand off.
-太好了  这就都安排好了  -哇  老妈
- Great, then we're all set. - Wow, mom.
现在你要回去工作了  我猜这是我们最后一次
Now that you're going back to work I guess this is our last
艾米·邓肯的私房早餐了吧  嗯
Amy Duncan home cooked breakfast, huh?
恐怕是的  宝贝
I'm afraid so, honey.
我知道你们都在干什么
I know what you're all doing.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>"Has anybody seen my left shoe?"</i>
■
翻译： Crazy王
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof.</i>
■
校订： Enpistu
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I survived.</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice.</i>
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃  不要怀疑
<i>Hang in there, baby, there's no maybe.</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right.</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down.</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me, it comes back around.</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love who you turn out to be.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第十三集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E13  Teddy and the Bambino
维克多·戴力士先生 大驾光临
There he is. Mr. Victor Deleseur.
两次南高中学生联合国的大赢家
Two-time winner of the South High student U.N.
三次  你好  泰迪
Three-time. Hello, Teddy.
找我有何贵干
Why'd you want to see me?
那个  很遗憾你和维多利亚分手了
Well, I was saddened to hear that you and Victoria broke up.
她说我不够浪漫
She said I wasn't romantic enough.
这完全不符合事实
Which is totally untrue.
按我的算法计算  结果指出我的浪漫指数高于平均值
I did an algorithm which proved my romanticism is above average.
无论如何  嗯
Anyway, um...
既然你和维多利亚不在一起了  我
Since you and Victoria are no longer together I...
嗯  打住
Uh, stop.
在你抱有任何希望之前
Before you get your hopes up,
我还没打算开始另一段恋情
I'm not ready to start another relationship.
太快了
It's too soon.
真的  好吧  嗯嗯
Really? Okay, um...
让我调整一下
Give me a moment to regroup...
好了
Done.
无论如何  嗯
Anyways, um...
我想你是否想和我做搭档
I was wondering if you actually wanted to
参加这次中学生联合国大会
be my partner for the student U.N.
啊  那你想赢得这个你每年都输掉的奖项
Ah, so you'd like to win the award you lose every year.
啊啊  不只是这样啦
Well, that's not all of it.
要有这份奖项 你的大学申请书会更具竞争力
Because the award will look good on your college applications,
很可能帮你进入一所很好的学校
and help you get into a better school.
对  这就是我的全部企图
Yeah. That's all of it.
各位 注意了
Attention everyone.
我回来了
I'm back!
耶
Yeah!
谢谢  谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
你们现在可以去抬那个尸体了
You guys can go pick up that corpse now.
哦  卡伦
Oh! Karen.
你好  邓肯
Hello, Duncan.
嗨  我以为你结婚后就不干护士了呢
Hi. I thought you gave up nursing after you got married.
是的  恩  我离婚了
Yeah, well, I'm not married any more.
他说我又专横有跋扈  可我觉得他对我不忠
He said I was loud and bossy, I think he has commitment issues.
嗯嗯  这个  嗯
Well, it's, uh...
能再次见到你真好
Nice to see you again.
是吗  邓肯
Is it, Duncan?
是吗
Is it?
因为我记得上次咱俩
Because I remember what happened
在这屋子里发生了什么事
the last time we were in this room together.
你记得吗
Do you?
我想我辞职是因为一个临时的小误会
I believe I resigned due to a temporary misunderstanding.
你拿个盐水袋朝我脸上喷
You popped one of these saline bags and squirted it in my face!
意思差不多啦
Tomato, to-mah-to.
我会盯着你的  邓肯
I'm keeping my eye on you, Duncan.
休完产假回来的护士可有很多问题呢
I've had a lot of problems with nurses returning from maternity leave.
你可不能像这样  哇哇哇  我好想我的宝宝
You're not gonna be all like "wah wah wah I miss my baby."
你会吗
Are you?
当然不会
Of course not.
很好
Good.
我要像这样  哇哇哇
I'm gonna be all "wah wah wah
难以置信我又要和你一起工作了
I can't believe I have to work with you again."
好了 这就是我们的演讲
Now, here is our presentation.
并且既然我们代表意大利  我决定在封皮上画个小小的
And since we're Italy, I decided to draw a nice little
地图在上面
map of our nation on the cover.
哦  很好  那是意大利
Oh, good. That's Italy.
注：意大利在地图上的形状像个靴子
我还以为画的是你要买的靴子呢
I was afraid you were drawing some boots that you wanted.
听着  我才不画靴子呢  我没那么肤浅
Look, I don't draw boots. I'm not that shallow.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  走吧
All right. Let's go.
你为何要带上这个小宝宝
Why are you taking the baby?
别担心  我爸会去学校找我
Don't worry. My Dad's gonna meet me at school
我就把托比传球给他
and we're gonna do a hand off.
就像橄榄球那样
Like in football.
无论如何  没事的
Anyway, it'll be fine.
托比真是个好宝贝  我们都没注意到他在这
Toby's such a sweet little boy, we won't even know he's there.
睡吧  小宝贝  不要出声
<i>Hush little baby don't say a word.</i>
你为什么要唱歌  孩子都这么不高兴了
Why are you singing? The child is obviously in distress.
注：能模仿别的鸟叫的鸟
爸爸给你买个反舌鸟
<i>Papa's gonna buy you a mockingbird.</i>
看见没
See?
太绝了
Amazing.
我家里禁止出现摇篮曲
Lullabies were forbidden in my house.
我母亲只允许我听18世纪的意大利歌剧
My mother would only allow me to listen to 18th century Italian operas.
哦  这就是为啥你变成
Oh, so that's why you turned out to be...
你这样
The way that you are.
你被喵喵警长逮捕了
"You've been arrested by a Sheriff Kitty.
去狗栏拘留所去
Go to the dog pound."
我就不懂了
I don't get it.
这游戏叫做  狗狗镇  但是警长却是只猫
The game's called "puppy town". But the Sheriff's a cat?
好吧  啊
Okay. Ah.
你又赢了  查莉
You win again, Charlie.
连赢十把
The 10th straight time.
- 再玩一次  -不不不不不不
- Play again? -No no no no no no.
不要  狗狗镇  了  我快要
No more "puppy town." I'm all...
我快要狗刨了
I'm all puppied out.
咱们来干点别的吧  我给你读本书吧
Let's do something else. Want to read a book?
好吧
Okay.
回归狗狗镇
"Return to puppy town."
我手机在楼上  等一下
My phone's upstairs. Hang on.
盖比  该你看查莉了
Gabe? It's your turn to watch Charlie.
等一下
Just a minute!
你说啥
What'd you say?
嗯
Eh.
查莉
Charlie?
你是不是跑出来了
Did you run away?
若果是的话  我不怪你
Because if you did, I don't blame you.
想玩吗
Want to play?
啊 狗狗镇  嗯
Oh, "puppy town," huh?
我以前和我儿子罗德尼玩
I used to play with my son Rodney.
我可得告诉你  这个我很拿手
I have to warn you, I'm pretty good.
我也是
Me too.
好吧  狗狗镇达人
Okay, hotshot.
这是我的小宝宝  托比
And this is my baby, Toby.
他待不待人亲
Isn't he adorable?
哦  你知道什么会待人亲
Oh, you know what would be adorable?
好好干你的活
Doing your job!
你见过我到处向人家炫耀我养的花草吗
You don't see me going around showing everyone pictures of my plant.
花草
A plant.
太聪明了  你终于有了个跑不了的东西了
How wise of you to get something that can't run away.
给自己的提醒
Note to self:
照张植物的照片  让人看
Take picture of plant, make people look at it.
好了  我要给你测血压了  富兰克林先生
Okay, I'm just going to check your blood pressure, Mr. Franklin.
你可以叫我托比
You can call me Toby.
哦  托比
Oh, Toby.
那是我宝贝的名字
That's my baby's name.
哦  想不到这么凑巧
Well, what do you know about that.
今天是我第一天回来工作  我太想他了
Today's my first day back at work, and I just miss him so much.
哦 托比
Oh, Toby.
-你弄疼我了  -哦  不会的  宝贝
- You're hurting me.  -Oh, no, sweetie.
妈咪永远不会伤害你  妈咪爱你
I would never hurt you. Mama loves you.
嘿  我胳膊没知觉了
Hey, I can't feel my arm.
啥
What?
抱歉  太抱歉了  富兰克林先生
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Mr. Franklin.
我今天不太容易集中精力
I'm just having a little trouble focusing today.
没关系  亲爱的
That's okay, dear.
你在医院工作  没必要专心于你的工作
You work in a hospital, no need to focus on your job.
谢谢你的理解
Thank you for understanding.
读啥呢
What you reading?
回归狗狗镇
"Return to puppy town."
你知道吗  我就搞不懂这喵喵警官
You know, I can't get past Sheriff Kitty.
我是说  为啥狗狗们要听一只猫的
I mean, why would dogs obey a cat?
谢了
Thank you.
好吧
Okay.
嗯  查莉呢
So, where's Charlie?
那真有意思  我也来
That's funny. I'll do it.
嗯  查莉呢
"So, where's Charlie?"
我以为他跟你在一起
I thought she was with you.
"I thought she was with you."
老兄  你为啥笑
Dude, why are you laughing?
因为你装作一副不知道查莉在哪里的样子
Because you're pretending you don't know where Charlie is.
我真不知道查莉在哪
I don't know where Charlie is!
什么
What?
-这突然间一点都不好玩了  -你以为
-This is suddenly not funny.  -You think?
我们的找到她  嗯  查莉
We got to find her. Uh, Charlie?
-查莉  -查莉
- Charlie?  -Charlie?
嘿  小子们
Hey, guys.
嘿  老爹
Hey, Dad.
你们在做什么呢
What are you doing?
嗯
Uh...
我们在和查莉玩捉迷藏
Playing hide-and-go-seek with Charlie.
是啊  她非常能藏
Yeah. She's very good.
-你想帮我们一起找吗  -她可能藏在任何地方  在这个屋子里
- You want to help us look?  - She could be anywhere in the house.
或屋子外
Or outside.
-游戏规则有点不明确  -是的
-The rules were kind of vague.  -Yeah.
哦  嘿  我有个主意
Oh, hey. Here's an idea.
你们为什么不去找隔壁的达布尼太太
Why don't you guys go next door  and look in Mrs. Dabney's house.
想知道为什么我叫你们去那吗
Do you want to know why I think you should go over and look there?
因为你不太会玩捉迷藏
Because you're not very good at this game?
不是  因为一小时前达布尼太太给我打电话
No, because Mrs. Dabney called me an hour ago
告诉我查莉去她那儿了
to tell me that Charlie had gone over there.
自己一个人去的
All by herself.
哦
Oh.
这样啊
So...
过程有一点点痛苦  但是结局圆满  是吧  老爸
A little moment of panic, but a happy ending, huh, Dad?
去接她
Go get her.
啊  等你俩小子回来  咱们的好好谈谈了
Oh, and when you guys come back we're having a little talk.
喵喵警长
Sheriff Kitty?
啊  这说不通耶
Well, that doesn't make any sense.
-维克多  -维多利亚
- Victor.  -Victoria.
这就是你的搭档
This is who you're partnered with?
泰迪·邓肯
Teddy Duncan?
她是个学术小白（痴）
She's academically inferior.
她不是小白 是大白（痴）
She's not inferior, she's marginal.
请就坐  伙计们
Sitting right here, guys.
现在  不好意思  我要带领挪威走向胜利
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm going to lead Norway to victory.
她当然是挪威了
Of course she would be Norway.
又冰  又自立  但是还是难以抗拒
Cold, isolated, yet irresistible.
老爸  你在哪
Dad, where are you?
什么
What?
哦  天啊  好吧  好吧  行
Oh, man. Okay. Yeah, okay.
只要快点来就行了
Just get here as fast as you can.
好了 拜
Okay, bye.
坏消息
Bad news.
嗯  我老爸要迟到了
Um, my Dad is running late,
我们恐怕还得和小宝贝多待一会儿了
so we're kind of stuck with the baby for a little while.
什么  我们可不能带个婴儿做演讲
What? We can't give our presentation with a baby.
好了  放松  都没人知道他在这
Okay, relax. No one will even know he's here.
是啊  除非他们能闻得到
Yeah, unless they have a sense of smell.
天啊 托比
Man, Toby.
又来了
Again?
好吧 我给你换
All right, let me change you.
真的  在这
Really? Right here?
这可是十分不
This is highly inappro...
维克多  你还好吧
Victor, are you okay?
没事  我再躺一会儿
Fine. Just gonna stay down here for a minute.
也许这不是个好主意
Probably not a good idea.
欢迎来到第十四届
Welcome to the 14th annual,
南高中学生联合国大赛
South High student united nations competition.
就像我经常在此刻要说的
As I always say at this juncture...
比赛开始
Game on.
好的  主席认得挪威代表
Yes, the chair recognizes the delegate from Norway.
谢谢  主席先生
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
我抗议意大利代表团
I would like to protest the fact that the Italian delegation
由三个人组成
appears to consist of three people.
最大人数只是两人
The maximum allowed is two.
意大利  想反驳吗
Italy, care to rebut?
嗯  第三个人是个小婴儿
Um, the third person is a baby.
婴儿也是人
A baby is a human being.
意大利已承认违反规章制度
Italy has admitted to breaking the rules
应当按程序将其驱出
and should be dismissed from the proceedings.
她很棒吧
Isn't she magnificent?
主席先生  意大利涉入了家庭看管问题
Mr. Chairman, Italy is involved in some family care issues,
意大利的父亲理应此刻到场  可如各位所见
Italy's father promised to be here, but as we can see
他没能顺利通过边界
he has failed to cross the border.
这个主席理解
The chair understands...
以前跟意大利的父母打过交道
Having dealt with Italy's parents before.
两个六点  你又赢了
Double sixes? You win again.
弄好  还没完呢
Set 'em up. This isn't over.
很好  只花了73分钟才让你们注意到
Well, it only took you 73 minutes to
你们的小妹妹不见了
realize your little sister was missing.
其实我们是
In our defense...
你没啥说的吗
You got anything?
-没  -哦
- Nope. -Oh.
查莉  你在这啊
Charlie, there you are.
哦  还在玩狗狗镇  是吧
Oh, playing "puppy town," huh?
-玩的怎么样  -平手
- How you doing? - It's about even.
不  不是
No, it's not.
-我故意让她赢的  -她说假话
- I let her win. -She said bad words.
赶快给她带走
Just take her and get out.
注：ICU 是重症病房
请埃利奥特医生到ICU  请埃利奥特医生到ICU
Dr. Elliot to ICU. Dr. Elliot to ICU.
妈咪  我看见你了
Mommy, I see you.
查莉
Charlie?
查莉  是你吗
Charlie, is that you?
你在跟谁说话呢
Who are you talking to?
嗯嗯  没人
Um, no one.
纳皮尔医生正在找你呢
Dr. Napier's looking for you.
哦  还有明天你要加班
Oh, and tomorrow, you're working a double.
干得漂亮  卡伦  这手法驾驭的
Good for you, Karen. Way to take the reins.
纳皮尔医生  你找我
Dr. Napier, you wanted to see me?
是的  我想让你回家  妈妈咪
Yes, I want you to come home, mommy.
嗯  不好意思
Uh, excuse me?
我想你了  妈咪
I miss you, mommy.
你想我了
You do?
能抱抱我吗
Can I have a hug?
当然了  哦哦
Of course you can. Ohh.
你在干什么呢  邓肯
What are you doing, Duncan?
综上所述挪威认为当今世界所面临的
And that is why Norway believes that the most important
最严峻问题就是债务问题  谢谢
problem facing the world today is debt. Thank you.
现在让我们有请意大利代表团
We will now hear from the Italian delegation.
谢谢主席先生
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
意大利认为当今世界面临的
Italy believes the most important issue
最严峻难题是环境问题
facing the world today is the environment.
继续
Just keep going.
正如我先前所述
As I was saying...
做点什么  别让他哭了
Do something. Make him be quiet.
只有唱歌才好用
Only singing will do that.
那我们该怎么办  把演讲唱出来
What are we supposed to do, sing the presentation?
意大利  我们正在等你们呢
Italy, we're waiting.
耶  主意不错  快唱吧
Yeah, that's a great idea. Just sing it.
-但我    -唱
- But I... -Sing.
积雪正在融逝
<i>The snow caps are melting.</i>
逃离世间的污染
<i>From all the pollution.</i>
我们的阿尔卑斯啊  他们在求援
<i>Our alps, they need helping.</i>
有一策良计
<i>There is a solution.</i>
向前进  向前进  向前进
<i>We will go, we will go, we will go.</i>
全军出击 全力以赴
<i>To hand our resolution in.</i>
如此一来
<i>So...</i>
你将知晓  你将知晓  你将知晓
<i>You will know, you will know, you will know.</i>
此战  我们志在必得
<i>It's a fight, we truly can win.</i>
好了  我刚把查理哄上床睡觉了  咱们得好好谈谈
All right, I just put Charlie down for her nap, so let's talk.
你们两个怎么能如此不负责任
How could you two be so irresponsible?
老爸  在我们开始之前  我们给你做了点东东
Dad, before we get into that, we made you a little something.
哦  好香啊  这个是鲍伯香鸡派吗
Oh, sweet Mama, is that a chicken Bob-pie?
么  么
Mm-hmm.
原料混入了切达干酪  迷你热狗  还有洋葱圈
Stuffed with cheddar cheese, mini hot dogs, and onion rings.
还有爱
And love.
不  不
No. No.
听着  小子们 贿赂不好用的
Look, guys, bribery is not gonna work.
我对你俩太失望了
I'm very disappointed in you two.
我现在不能在这里做所有事
Now, I can't do everything around here.
我本应该去学校接托比
I was supposed to be over at the high school to pick up Toby,
可是现在我却在整这些
but now I gotta deal with this.
抱歉  老爸
We're sorry, Dad.
我就是不敢相信你们就那么让查莉从大门走出去了
I just can't believe you would let Charlie walk right out that door.
老爸  我们保证这再也不会发生了
Dad, we won't let it happen again.
很好
Good.
好了 要是我们没事了  我记得刚刚有提过派
Now if we're done, I believe there was a pie mentioned.
现在最激动人心的时刻终于来到
And now the exciting moment that we've all been waiting for...
第十四届南高中学生联合国大赛的获奖得主是
The winner of the 14th annual South High student U.N. competition is...
哦  我的神啊  是意大利
Oh, my goodness. Italy.
太棒了  我们赢了
Yes! We won!
维克多
Victor?
我还不知道你能唱出那样的歌
I didn't know you could sing like that.
太浪漫了
It was so romantic.
这表示你想让我回来吗
Does this mean you want me back?
-你在问64的平方是  -4096
- Is 64 the square root of...  -4,096?
哦  亲爱的
Oh, darling.
恭喜   意大利
Congratulations, Italy.
哇哇  嗯嗯
Wow, um...
要知道  我得要谢谢这个小小人
You know, I'd like to thank the little people.
小小人  我是说托比
And by little people, I mean Toby.
爱你  小弟
Love you, bro.
嗨  伙计们
Hey, guys.
嗨  老妈  怎会下班这么早
Hey, mom. What are you doing home from work so early?
哦  今天糟透了
Oh, I had a terrible day.
我老是有些托比和查莉的疯狂幻想觉
I kept having these crazy hallucinations about Toby and Charlie.
事实上  它们现在还有
In fact, they're still going on.
我想我刚刚在布达尼太太家的窗户上看见查莉了
I thought I just saw Charlie in Mrs.Dabney's window.
嗯  真疯了
Well, that's crazy.
妈咪
Mommy!
还有人能看见她吗
Does anyone else see her?
她又跑出来了
She got out again.
这儿的手术做的不错嘛
Some operation you're running here.
但是  是他们先弄丢的
But... They lost her first!
-什么  -他吃了三个派
- What?!  -He ate three pies.
-是啊  -你们给我做的
- Yeah!  -Because you made them for me.
都闭嘴
Quiet everybody!
吃货  厨房去  马上
Pie boy, in the kitchen now!
你俩好好看着你妹妹
And you two watch your sister.
宝贝宝贝宝贝  好了 听着  我能解释
Honey honey honey, okay, look. I can explain.
我知道这看上去很糟
I know it looks bad.
鲍伯  我今天太想他俩了
Bob, I missed the kids so much today.
回去工作比我想象得要难得多
Going back to work is so much harder than I thought.
宝贝  这只是第一天  会好起来的
Honey, it's just the first day. It's gonna get better.
我不知道
I don't know.
鲍伯  我们有两个小不点  他们都需要我
Bob, we have two little ones now, and they both need me so much.
我就是
I just...
听着  我知道我们需要钱
Look, I know we need the money,
可要是我能在家里
but if there's a way I could stay home...
好吧 好吧好吧  听着  要是这样做对家里好的话
Okay, all right all right, look, if this is what's best for the family.
那么我们就  就找个法子
Then we'll... We'll find a way.
哦 鲍伯
Oh, Bob.
好吧
Okay.
看样子我得回医院辞职去了
Guess I'd better go back to the hospital and quit.
-打电话不行吗  -因为是卡伦
- Can't you do that over the phone?  - It's Karen.
我得亲自动手
I should do it in person.
你好  卡伦
Hello, Karen.
-那是给病人用的吗  -不是滴
- Is that for a patient? - Nope.
-你要辞职  -是滴
- You quitting? -Yup.
我能先戴上泳镜吗
Do I have time to put on my goggles?
我最近买了副泳镜因为我有预感
I recently bought goggles because I had a feeling.
不行滴
Nope.
哇  哦  哦
Whoa! Oh! Oh no!
哦
Ohh...
干得漂亮  艾米  干得漂亮
Good for you, Amy. Good for you.
好了  查莉  看样子妈妈要在家里待一阵子了
Well, Charlie, it looks like mom's gonna be staying at home for a while.
还有鉴于咱家买了新的儿童锁
And since we got new childproof locks,
希望你也可以老实在家待着
we are hoping you will be too.
不  不过说真的  妈妈在家太好了
No, but seriously, it's gonna be really great to have mom at home.
对你  对托比  还有呵呵 对我们大家都好
For you, and for Toby, and yeah, well, for all of us.
早饭好了
Breakfast is ready.
再等一分钟
Better give it a minute.
你要一日三餐都和她在一起了
You're gonna be with her for three meals a day.
祝你好运啰  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
您好  邓肯夫人
<i>Hello, Mrs. Duncan.</i>
有些事我不得不说
<i>I've something I must say.</i>
我洗耳恭听  维克多
<i>Then let's hear it, Victor.</i>
我日理万机  有话快说
<i>I don't have all day.</i>
自从我与维多利亚复合
<i>Since I'm back with Victoria.</i>
泰迪和我
<i>Teddy and I..</i>
就没有  啦
<i>Are no more-ia.</i>
我想你误会了
<i>I think you're mistaken.</i>
泰迪已经有主了
<i>Teddy's already taken.</i>
嘿  你们在做什么呢
Hey. What's going on?
亲爱的  你不知道吗
<i>Honey don't you know?</i>
我们就是这样的
<i>We're singing as..</i>
唱
<i>We go.</i>
但是我不会唱
But I can't sing.
-你必须唱  -你必须唱
<i>- You must.  -You must.</i>
<i>- You must.  - You must.</i>
你要和我们一起唱
<i>You must sing with us.</i>
玛丽有只小羊羊
<i>Mary had a little lamb.</i>
小羊羊
<i>Little lamb.</i>
-得了吧得了吧  -是啊  太糟糕了
-Forget it. Forget it. -Yeah, that was terrible.
有人朝我家玻璃扔了个球
<i>Somebody threw a ball through my window.</i>
谁来修
<i>Who's gonna fix..</i>
别别别别  我们再也不那么唱了
No no no no. We're not doing that any more.
我为什么要配合你们这些人
Why do I even try with you people?